{
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "physics"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "chemistry"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "name": "maths"
    }
  ],
  "physics": [
    {
      "question": "Which device is required for the Internet connection?",
      "option1": "Modem",
      "option2": "Router",
      "option3": "LAN Cabel",
      "option4": "Pen Drive",
      "ans": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which device is required for the ?",
      "option1": "Modem",
      "option2": "Router",
      "option3": "LAN Cabel",
      "option4": "Pen Drive",
      "ans": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which  Internet connection?",
      "option1": "Modem",
      "option2": "Router",
      "option3": "LAN Cabel",
      "option4": "Pen Drive",
      "ans": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "Which device is required for the connection?",
      "option1": "Modem",
      "option2": "Router",
      "option3": "LAN Cabel",
      "option4": "Pen Drive",
      "ans": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which device is Internet connection?",
      "option1": "Modem",
      "option2": "Router",
      "option3": "LAN Cabel",
      "option4": "Pen Drive",
      "ans": 2
    }
  ],
  "chemistry": [
    {
      "question": "What is the first element on the periodic table?",
      "option1": "Hydrogen",
      "option2": "Carbon",
      "option3": "Oxygen",
      "option4": "Nitrogen",
      "ans": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the centre of an atom called?",
      "option1": "Hydrogen",
      "option2": "Carbon",
      "option3": "Oxygen",
      "option4": "Nitrogen",
      "ans": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the second element on the periodic table?",
      "option1": "Hydrogen",
      "option2": "Carbon",
      "option3": "Oxygen",
      "option4": "Nitrogen",
      "ans": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the third element on the periodic table?",
      "option1": "Hydrogen",
      "option2": "Carbon",
      "option3": "Oxygen",
      "option4": "Nitrogen",
      "ans": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the fourth element on the periodic table?",
      "option1": "Hydrogen",
      "option2": "Carbon",
      "option3": "Oxygen",
      "option4": "Nitrogen",
      "ans": 1
    }
  ],
  "maths": [
    {
      "question": "What is the sum of 130+125+191?",
      "option1": "365",
      "option2": "456",
      "option3": "446",
      "option4": "232",
      "ans": 1
    },
    {
      "question": " If we minus 712 from 1500, how much do we get?",
      "option1": "778",
      "option2": "123",
      "option3": "343",
      "option4": "43",
      "ans": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "50 times of 8 is equal to:",
      "option1": "400",
      "option2": "4000",
      "option3": "40000",
      "option4": "400000",
      "ans": 4
    }
  ]
}
